<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julian Lore</title>
    <link>https://julianlore.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Julian Lore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Julian Lore 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 14:27:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://julianlore.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Github Releases</title>
      <link>https://julianlore.com/blog/automating-github-releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 14:27:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianlore.com/blog/automating-github-releases/</guid>
      <description>Github releases are a good way to distribute milestone releases of your repository and in particular, releasing binary files such that others do not necessarily need to recompile from source.
Note: If you want to simply just mark milestones of your repository, you can use the git tag feature. Tags pushed to Github will be in the releases area of your repository and offer users the option to download a zip or tar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing an Arch Linux VM</title>
      <link>https://julianlore.com/blog/installing_arch_linux_vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 22:24:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianlore.com/blog/installing_arch_linux_vm/</guid>
      <description>I use Arch Linux as my main working operating system on my laptop, as I love how it is very bare-bones and can be configured exactly how you like it, making it your very own experience, but at the same time not requiring as much maintenance such as Gentoo or Linux From Scratch, although I have yet to try others. I do respect the many other Linux distributions, as I have tried many and like them (and see their usability), just not as much as something that I can make my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website!</title>
      <link>https://julianlore.com/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:55:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianlore.com/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website! Welcome to my personal website. After having my old website up for a bit over two years and not updating it for a long time, I have decided to switch from a static website with raw HTML to a generated static website using Hugo. Haven&amp;rsquo;t decided completely as to what to put on here yet, aside from my personal portfolio, showcasing some projects and perhaps some resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>